# JIUN T.WANG

- + GRAPHIC DESIGNER
- + DIGITAL MARKETER
- + WEB DEVELOPER

# Hi there!

I'm a Graphic Designer, Digital Marketer, and Front-End Web Developer, specializing in branding, logo design, web/print design, infographics, email marketing, social media ads, content management, working with HTML/CSS, analytics reporting, and list segmentation for targetting.

jiuntwang@gmail.com · jiuntingwang.com

### **EDUCATION-**

# SEATTLE UNIVERSITY

Web & Application Technology Sept 2016 - Aug 2017

Front-End Web Development
Professional Certificate

#### UNIVERSITY AT BUFFALO

Department of Art & Design Jan 2009 - May 2012

**Graphic Design Concentration**B.A. Studio Art

# SKILLS \_

ADVANCED			NTERMEDIATE	BEGINNER
Photoshop CC Illustrator CC InDesign CC  Vertical Response Constant Contact MailChimp Infusionsoft  HTML CSS, SCSS	Google Analytics Facebook Ads WordPress Wix, Squarespace Sketch, InVision  MS Word MS PowerPoint MS Excel Dropbox Slack, Skype Trello		Drupal 6/8 Git, GitHub Bootstrap  Salesforce Pardot Magento Zeplin Basecamp Wistia	JavaScript AngularJS Yeoman Grunt, Gulp API's

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# DESIGN & DIGITAL MARKETING SPECIALIST Sept 2017 - Current

Strategic Dentistry - A Dental Marketing Agency (Seattle, WA)

- O Devising strategies to drive online traffic to the company website; evaluating customer research, market conditions, and competitor data; tracking conversion rates; improving usability, design, content, and conversion of the marketing campaigns.
- Responsible for creating the look and f eel of the company's website and email campaigns. This involves developing a graphic design and content that effectively communicates the ideas being promoted by the website and organization.
- Design and create mini-site and landing pages; design, code, and send responsive HTML emails to large mailing lists; design site content and graphics by coordinating with copywriters and graphic artists.
- $\diamondsuit$  Review new technologies and keep the company at the forefront of developments in digital marketing.

#### GRAPHIC & WEB DESIGNER Jul 2016 - Current

Freelancer - self-employed (Seattle, WA)

- O Working on individual projects ranging from logos, print and web advertisements, illustrations, book covers, apparel design, info-graphics, mail campaigns, event signage, landing pages, and more.
- I provide multiple sketches, wireframes, and mock-ups during the designing process to make sure the client and I are on the same page in regards to the visual aesthetics.
- Recent Clients: Falafel Salem, Mandarin House, RankedBlogs, Megan Otis, Unbelievably Clean, and Granite Sports Institute.

## GRAPHIC & MARKETING COORDINATOR Jan 2015 - Jul 2016

Orogem Corporation - A Fine Jewelry Manufacturer (Burbank, CA)

- O Lead for the in-house Marketing Department, responsible for ensuring brand consistency across company ads and planning marketing campaigns to specific customer demographics.
- Worked directly with VP of Design to create sales sheets and catalogs.
- Managed website redesign by providing wireframes, notes, QA testing per task for the web development team. Updated website banners, product images, descriptions, and costs using Magento's CMS. Provided vendors with custom image libraries for their own website use. Photographed jewelry and traced and retouched images for web and print marketing.

W	/ O	D K	FX	PFI	DIF	N <sub>C</sub>	F	(continued)
•		R N	^		~	11 ~	_	COHHILIDEAL

## **GRAPHIC DESIGNER** May 2012 - Sept 2014

# FRSGear, LLC - Custom Apparel Design for Schools and Athletics (Westlake Village, CA)

Oraphic Designer for schools and sports team's needs for custom apparel and sales flyers for their uniforms and fundraising events.

Trained in using a digital garment printer, vinyl cutter, heatpress.

Designed graphics for shirts, hoodies, hats, stickers, bags, sell sheets, event flyers, banners, posters, email newsletters, social media and web graphics. Products were created using digital printing, screen printing, embroidery, or materials consisting of metallics, glitter, and vinyl.

# SEO CONTENT WRITER INTERN May 2012 - Aug 2012

# Ontrix Solutions - A Online Marketing Company (Woodland Hills, CA)

Ocontent Writer for multiple websites; researched and wrote content using specific keywords in relation to the location, name, and industry of the business.

) Served as an assistant Web Designer by creating wireframes, creating a list of design implementation tasks, and QA testing of the company's website.